35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans], circa 1963; 8 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thomas writing something], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Lowell Thoams talking with two women next to a group of children], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children dressed in colorful robes], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Three people dressed in colorful robes standing next to Lowell Thomas], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Crowd of children walking beside building], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Children putting on a performance], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Children putting on a performance], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Building], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Building], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Crowd of children walking beside building], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans], circa 1963; 9 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children waving to camera], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children waving to camera], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Line of children walking], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children gathered outside of a building], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children gathered outside of a building], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children walking], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children gathered outside of a building, surrounding a unique structure], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Line of children, putting on a performance], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Line of children, putting on a performance], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Line of children walking], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Children in colorful robes putting on a performance], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of little boys], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing a bright yellow robe], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children putting on a performance], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing a fur hat], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing a fur hat and colorful robe], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Woman wearing a colorful robe], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Two men and two women wearing colorful robes], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Woman wearing a colorful robe], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man and woman wearing colorful robes], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans], circa 1963; 10 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of people wearing colorful robes, holding a flag], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of people wearing colorful robes, holding a flag], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Group of children wearing colorful robes], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Men wearing colorful robes and fur hats], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man with a colorful robe and a fur hat], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Women wearing colorful robes and holding a flag], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing a fur hat and a red robe], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Children wearing colorful robes, Lowell Thomas standing next to them], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Two women and a man wearing colorful robe], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Person wearing a colorful robe], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing colorful robe], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Woman wearing colorful robe], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Person wearing colorful robe], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Man wearing colorful robe and fur hat], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Two people in colorful robes], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Four women in colorful robes holding a flag], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Three people in colorful robes], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Two people in colorful robes], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Four people in colorful robes], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 3 [India; visit with the Dalai Lama and other Tibetans]: Two women wearing colorful robes], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)], undated; 11 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)] [: Mountain], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountain], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountain], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountain], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Body of water and mountains], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountain], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Four people standing together in colorful robes, Lowell Thomas at left], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Four people standing together in colorful robes], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountains], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Line of children], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Line of children], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Line of children], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Bottom of a mountain], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Mountain], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Native American men with feathered headdress], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Native American men with feathered headdress], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Native American men with feathered headdress], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: A prairie dog], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: A prairie dog], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 4 [Glacier Park (Lowell Thomas, Jr.)]: Small waterfall], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], circa early 1940s; 12 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] [: Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s profile], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Swimming pool], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Lowell Thomas, Jr. near mountainside], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Lowell Thomas, Jr. leaning against vehicle], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]:Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s profile ], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]:Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s profile ], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]:Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s profile ], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]:Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s profile ], 8
  - Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], circa early 1940s; 13 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: River and mountains], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Snowy mountains], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Man looking at snowy mountain], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Mountains], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Mountains], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Snowy mountain], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Mountain], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: Body of water, building in front of mountain view], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 5 [Lowell Thomas, Jr.]: River running by mountains], 9
  - Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill], 1940; 14 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill] [: Garden], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Mailbox with a sign that says "Road to Ball Park Closed], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: A white house], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: A white house], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Frances Ryan Thomas holding a dog], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Frances Ryan Thomas feeding the dog a treat outside], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Flower garden], 7
  - Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill], 1940; 15 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: A white house], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: View of house, pine trees and mountains], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Line of cherry trees], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: A swimming pool], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Side of a white house], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 6 [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at Quaker Hill]: Side of a white house], 6
  - Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)], circa 1971; 16 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)] [: Road in a forest], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Road runing through a forest], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Truck driving through a forest on a dirt road], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: In a forest], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: In a forest], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: In a forest], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Two men shaking hands by a parked car], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Crowd of people sitting on benches in a forest], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Creek running through forest], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Group of men talking outside], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Group of men talking], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man standing at a podium, speaking], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Close-up of a man], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Close-up of a man], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Group of men together, smiling], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Three men together, talking], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Two men talking], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man at podium, speaking], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Two men standing together], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Two men shaking hands], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)], circa 1971; 17 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Close-up of a man], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People putting on a stage performance], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Trees? (blurry photo)], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Close-up of a man], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People on stage, dancing], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man shooting a gun], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: A performance], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People putting on a performance], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People putting on a performance], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People putting on a performance], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People putting on a performance], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Cast gathered on stage, audience applauding], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Band on stage, performing], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man playing a piano], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People on a stage], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People laying out on field], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Choir on stage], 17
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man playing piano, another man sitting next to him on piano bench], 18
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on grass], 19
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People gathered, conversing], 20
  - Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)], circa 1971; 18 (Box 1591)
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting together], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Man conducting a choir], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting at a bar], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on stage], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on grass], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting on a bench], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Photos on display], 7
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on grass], 8
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on grass], 9
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting at a table], 10
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting outside eating, Lowell Thomas at left], 11
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: People sitting on rocks], 12
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting outside at tables, eating, Lowell Thoams standing on a platform, speaking], 13
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Band performing], 14
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting on ground, listening to band play], 15
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men sitting on ground], 16
    - [Kodachrome box number 7 [Outdoor gathering of men (possibly Bohemian Grove)]: Men standing around a bar], 17
  - Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California], undated; 19 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California] [: Close-up of a donkey], 1
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Snowy mountains], 2
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Snowy mountains], 3
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Man on skiis], 4
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Lowell Thomas with two other men on a snowy mountain], 5
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Two men on snowy mountain], 6
    - [Kodachrome box number 8 [Mineral King, California]: Snowy mountain], 7
  - Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates], 1949; 20 (Box 1591)
    - Beginning of Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates] [: Tibetans wearing robes in front of Potala Palace, laughing and smiling], 1
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Two Tibetans wearing robes in a garden], 2
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Tibetan painting], 3
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Close-up of pouring tea], 4
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Statue of an unearthly creature], 5
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thoma, Jr. with three Tibetan men in front of the Potala Palace], 6
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking with a Tibetan boy dressed in robes], 7
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Buildings in Tibet], 8
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Tibetan monks], 9
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Two Tibetan people around a smoking object], 10
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Tibetan monks gathered together], 11
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: People climbing the steps to the Potala Palace], 12
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Three Tibetan people dressed in robes], 13
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Tibetan man dressed in robes], 14
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: A bust Tibetan street], 15
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [Tibet duplicates]: Tibetan man in robes handing white cloth over to Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 16
  Box 1592
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 (continued from previous box) [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places], undated; 1 (Box 1592)
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: A harbor], 1
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: A flower garden with a little sign that reads "Lowell Thomas"], 2
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: A flower garden with a little sign that reads "Lowell Thomas"], 3
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: A man riding a horse], 4
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: People skiing], 5
    - [Kodachrome miscellaneous box 1 [slide 1: Lowell Thomas and others on ski slope [Alta, Utah?]; slide 2-3: Commercially purchased slides of Australasia; slide 4-5: The Lowell Thomas rose; slide 6: Conrad Hilton on horseback, circa 1964; remaining slides of unidentified people and places]: View from top of a mountain], 6